hometheater.com 2018-11-12

# 

### AVTech Media Americas PRIVACY POLICY 

**Overview**   
This Privacy Policy (the "Policy") discloses the privacy practices of AVTech Media Americas Media, Inc. This Policy governs how we use and protect personal information that we collect when you visit our website, use our services, or otherwise engage with us. Any practices or points that are specific to AVTech Media Americas are also clearly marked out in this Policy. 

Any use you make of AVTech Media Americas service offerings is subject to AVTech Media Americas's [Terms of Service (TOS)](http://www.avtechmediausa.com/terms.html). 

**About Us**   
AVTech Media Americas Media, Inc. has a principal office at located at 260 Madison Avenue (8th floor), New York, NY 10016, United States of America. 

If you have any questions about this Policy or questions or complaints about our privacy practices, please contact us using the details below: 

FAO: Data Protection Officer  
Address: AVTech Media Americas Media, Inc., 260 Madison Avenue (8th floor), New York, NY 10016, USA  
Email: [privacy@avtechmediausa.com](mailto:privacy@avtechmediausa.com)

The contact information above should also be used for communications relating to exercising the rights described in section 6.2 below. 

**1\. Information We Collect**

We collect personal information in the following ways: 

**1.1 Information that you provide to us directly**

We gather information that you provide to us when you: 

  * purchase products or services from us
  * subscribe to our newsletters and mailing lists
  * participate in promotional offers (such as a trial subscription) and other promotions, competitions or prize drawings
  * fill in forms, conduct searches, post content on the website, respond to surveys, or use any other features of our websites
  * make an inquiry, provide feedback, submit correspondence, or make a complaint over the phone, by email, on our website or by post
  * register for, and update an online account with us (including if you access through Facebook, Twitter, Google, or an open IP provider)
  * enter into a contract with us
  * contact other users on the websites, e.g. on the AVTech Media Americas various websites
  * 'follow', 'like', post to, or interact with, our social media accounts, including Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, Instagram, Google+, and Others.

The information you provide to us will include (depending on the circumstances): 

  * Identity and contact data: title, names, addresses, email addresses, phone numbers or your signature.
  * Account profile data: a username/display name, password, user preferences and, if you sign up through a social media account, certain information about that account.
  * Visual and audio information about yourself: e.g. a photo or video footage, or sound recording.
  * Your preferences: information about your preferences, interests, industry focus, community choices, and other customer profile information.
  * Any other information that you choose to share with us: for example, any information that you provide via correspondence, when you fill out our survey(s), that you share via our website or social media accounts linked to our website.

**1.2 Information we collect through technology related to our products and services**

Some of our products and services collect information about system and product data. We use this information to manage and administer our products and services, to issue updates and new versions, testing and monitoring services that we provide, enhancing our products and services, and improving and targeting our communications with you. 

**1.3 Information we collect through online technology**

Technologies such as cookies, beacons, tags, local storage, and scripts are used by us and our affiliates, and other companies, such as third party technology service providers and web analytics providers. These technologies make it easier for you to navigate our website and to help us manage the content on our website and are used to analyze trends, administer the sites, track users' movements around the site (including which site you clicked from to arrive at our site), and gather demographic information about our user base. 

**1.4 Information from other sources**

In certain circumstances, we will receive information about you from other sources, including third parties. For example, we may receive personal information from any of the following, who may be based inside and/or outside the EU: 

  * Other website users.
  * Your agents or representatives who are acting on your instructions.
  * Commercial contact lists that we acquire from other organizations.
  * Organizations that we acquire or merge with.
  * Organizations with whom we provide co-branded events, websites, products, and services.
  * Fraud detection agencies.
  * Social media plugins. By providing your social media account details you are authorizing that third-party provider to share with us certain information about you.

We might also receive information about you from other third parties if you have indicated to such third parties that you would like to hear from us. 

**1.5 Special categories of data**

We do not collect details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health and genetic and biometric data. Depending on the circumstances, we will also do not collect information about criminal convictions and offenses. 

**2\. Using Personal Information**

**2.1 How we use information we collect**

We use your information for the following purposes: 

  * To provide access to our website in a manner convenient and optimal and with personalized content relevant to you (on the basis of our legitimate interest to ensure our website is presented in an effective and optimal manner).
  * To register and maintain your AVTech Media Americas account (on the basis of performing our contract with you).
  * To monitor your account and use of services to ensure compliance with our end-user agreements and prevent and identify unlawful content use and violations (on the basis of our legitimate interests to operate a safe and lawful business, or where we have a legal obligation to do so).
  * To enable you to communicate with other website users and clients (on the basis of your consent where we have requested it, or on the basis of performing our contract with you).
  * To manage our relationship with you, which will include notifying you about changes to our terms of service or privacy policy, and asking you to leave a review or take a survey (on the basis of performing our contract with you, to comply with our legal obligations, and our legitimate interest in keeping our records updated and study how our website and services are used).
  * To provide customer service and support, like dealing with inquiries or complaints about the website, which may include sharing your information with our website developer, IT support provider, and payment services provider as necessary (on the basis of performing our contract with you, our legitimate interest in providing the correct products and services to our website users, and to comply with our legal obligations).
  * To enable you to take part in prize drawings, competitions, and surveys (on the basis of performing our contract with you, and our legitimate interest in studying how our website and services are used, to develop them, and to grow our business).
  * To carry out marketing and let you know about our news, events, new website features products or services that we believe may interest you, including sharing your information with our marketing services providers (either on the basis of your consent where we have requested it, or our legitimate interests to provide you with marketing communications where we may lawfully do so).
  * To deliver relevant website content and advertisements to you and measure or understand the effectiveness of the advertising we serve to you (on the basis of our legitimate interests in studying how our website/services are used, to develop them, to grow our business and to inform our marketing strategy).
  * To interact with users on social media platforms (on the basis of our legitimate interest in promoting our brand and communicating with interested individuals).
  * To conduct data analytics to improve our website, products/services, marketing, customer relationships and experiences (on the basis of our legitimate interests in defining types of customers for our website and services, to keep our website updated and relevant, to develop our business, to provide the right kinds of products and services to our customers, and to inform our business and marketing strategy).
  * To make suggestions and recommendations by sharing your information with selected third parties such as sponsors and partners, so they can contact you about things that may interest you (either on the basis of your consent where we have requested it, or on the basis of our legitimate interest to share details of conference attendees with our co-presenters and sponsors).
  * To carry out marketing research and user testing to assess the levels of satisfaction of existing and proposed products and services (on the basis of our legitimate interest in carrying out research, providing the right kinds of products and services to our customers).
  * To protect, investigate, and deter against fraudulent, unauthorized, or illegal activity (on the basis of our legitimate interests to operate a safe and lawful business, or where we have a legal obligation to do so).
  * To enable us to comply with our policies and procedures and enforce our legal rights, and to protect the rights, property or safety of our employees and share your information with our technical and legal advisors (on the basis of our legitimate interests to operate a safe and lawful business, or where we have a legal obligation to do so).

We will use your information for the purposes listed above either on the basis of: 

  * your consent (where we request it);
  * performance of your contract with us and the provision of our services to you;
  * where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation; or
  * our legitimate interests or those of a third party (see section 2.2 below for more information).

**2.2 Legitimate interests**

As outlined above, in certain circumstances we may use your personal information to pursue legitimate interests of our own or those of third parties. Where we refer to our "legitimate interests", we mean our legitimate business interests in conducting and managing our business and our relationship with you, including the legitimate interests we have specified in section 2.1 above. 

Where we use your information for our legitimate interests, we make sure that we take into account any potential impact that such use may have on you. Our legitimate interests don't automatically override yours and we won't use your information if we believe your interests should override ours unless we have other grounds to do so (such as your consent or a legal obligation). If you have any concerns about our processing please refer to details of "Your Rights" in Section 6 below. 

**3\. How We Share and Disclose Personal Information**

We consider your personal information to be a vital part of our relationship with you and do not sell your personal information to third parties. There are, however, certain circumstances in which we may share your personal information with certain third parties, as follows: 

  * Other website users and clients who use our websites and/or applications to communicate or otherwise interact with you;
  * Sponsors, partners and collaborators, including sponsors of our events, products or services, and organizations with whom we host co-branded events.
  * Our service providers who are acting as processors and who assist us with our administrative or business functions, or in the provision of any of our products/services to you.
  * Wholly owned subsidiaries, and foreign offices, of AVTech Media Americas Media, Inc.
  * Marketing parties which are any selected third party that you consent to our sharing your information with for marketing purposes.
  * Any prospective buyer of our business or assets, only in the event that we wish to sell any part of our business or assets.
  * Other third parties including legal, professional or other advisors, regulatory authorities, courts, law enforcement agencies and government agencies) where necessary to enable us to enforce our legal rights, or to protect the rights, property or safety of our employees or where such disclosure may be permitted or required by law.

**4\. How We Look After Your Personal Information and How Long We Keep It**

**4.1 Security**

We use administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to protect the security, confidentiality, and integrity of personal data against loss, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction. We also operate a policy of "privacy by design" by looking for opportunities to minimize the amount of personal information we hold about you. 

The safeguards we use include: 

  * ensuring the physical security of our offices, warehouses, or other sites
  * ensuring the physical and digital security of our equipment and devices by using appropriate password protection and encryption
  * using standard security protocols and mechanisms (such as secure socket layer (SSL) encryption) to transmit sensitive data such as credit card details
  * maintaining a data protection policy for, and delivering data protection training to, our employees
  * limiting access to your personal information to those who need to use it in the course of their work

If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, please contact us using the methods outlined in the "Contact Us" section above. 

**4.2 Retention**

We will keep your information for as long as is necessary to provide you with the services that you have requested from us or for as long as we reasonably require to retain the information for our lawful business purposes, such as for the purposes of exercising our legal rights or where we are permitted to do. We operate a data retention policy and look to find ways to reduce the amount of information we hold about you and the length of time that we need to keep it. 

Please contact us using the methods outlined in the "Contact Us" section above if you would like to obtain details of our retention periods for different aspects of your personal data. 

**4.3 Help keep your information safe**

You can also play a part in keeping your information safe by: 

  * choosing a strong account password, changing it regularly, and using different passwords for different online accounts
  * keeping your login and password details confidential
  * logging out of the website and closing the browser each time you have finished using it, especially when using a shared computer
  * informing us if know or suspect that your account has been compromised, or if someone has accessed your account without your permission
  * keeping your devices protected by using the latest version of your operating system and maintaining any necessary anti-virus software
  * being vigilant to any fraudulent emails that may appear to be from us. Any emails that we send will come from an email address ending in: @avtechmediausa.com (AVTech Media Americas)

**5\. International Transfers of Your Information**

AVTech Media Americas is based in the United States of America. 

**5.1 Special note to users outside of the United States**

We transact business throughout the world and have operations, processes and systems that cross borders. Our offices are located in the United States, and our servers are located in the United States and the United Kingdom. We transfer your personal data within the AVTech Media Americas group of brands in the United States, and to affiliates, joint venture partners, and third party service providers around the world. 

If you reside in the European Union, please be advised that your personal data will be processed outside of the European Economic Area (EEA). We will take all steps necessary to ensure that your information is adequately protected and processed in accordance with this Privacy Policy, including but not limited to: 

  * only transferring your personal data to countries that have been deemed to provide an adequate level of protection for personal data by the European Commission;
  * where we use providers based in the US, we may transfer data to them if they are part of the EU-US Privacy Shield which requires them to provide similar protection to personal data shared between the Europe and the US; or
  * where we use certain service providers, we may use specific contracts approved by the European Commission which give personal data the same protection it has in Europe (the so-called European Commission's Standard Contractual Clauses).

We may transfer your personal information to countries in the following regions outside of the EEA: North America and Asia. Please contact us using the contact details in this Privacy Policy if you want further information on the specific mechanism used by us when transferring your personal data out of the EEA. 

**6\. Your Rights: Access and Accuracy, Updating, Correcting, or Deleting Information**

**6.1 Your rights – summary**

You have certain rights in respect of the information that we hold about you, including: 

  * the right to be informed of the ways in which we use your information, as we seek to do in this Privacy Policy
  * the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes
  * the right to request access to the information that we hold about you
  * the right to request that we correct or rectify any information that we hold about you which is out of date or incorrect
  * the right to withdraw your consent for our use of your information in reliance of your consent (refer to section 2 above to see when we are relying on your consent), which you can do by contacting us using any of the details at the top of this Privacy Policy
  * the right to object to our using your information on the basis of our legitimate interests (refer to section 2 above to see when we are relying on our legitimate interests) (or those of a third party)) and there is something about your particular situation which makes you want to object to processing on this ground
  * the right to receive a copy of any information we hold about you (or request that we transfer this to another service provider) in a structured, commonly-used, machine readable format, in certain circumstances
  * in certain circumstances, the right to ask us to limit or cease processing or erase information we hold about you
  * the right to lodge a complaint about us to the UK Information Commissioner's Office (https://ico.org.uk/) as well as a right to lodge a complaint with the relevant authority in your country of work or residence

**6.2 How to exercise your rights**

You may exercise your rights above by contacting us using the methods outlined in the "Contact Us" section above and we will comply with your requests unless we have a lawful reason not to do so. 

In the case of preventing processing for marketing activities, you can opt out of marketing by signing in to your Safari account and updating your account settings. You may also opt-out of receiving newsletters or other communications by following the opt-out instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by contacting us using the methods outlined in the "Contact Us" section above. 

You can opt out of our Google Analytics data collection by using the tools available here: https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/ 

Please note that your objection to processing (or withdrawal of any previously given consent) could mean that we are unable to provide you with our services. Even after you have chosen to withdraw your consent we may continue to process your personal information when required or permitted by law, in particular in connection with exercising and defending our legal rights, or meeting our legal and regulatory obligations. 

**6.3 What we need from you to process your requests**

We may need to request specific information from you to help us confirm your identity and to enable you to exercise the rights set out above. This is a security measure to ensure that personal data is not disclosed to any person who has no right to receive it. We may also contact you to ask you for further information in relation to your request to speed up our response. 

You will not have to pay a fee to exercise the rights set out above. However, we may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive. Alternatively, we may refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances. We will try to respond to all legitimate requests within one month. Occasionally it may take us longer than a month if your request is particularly complex or you have made a number of requests. In this case, we will notify you and keep you updated. 

**7\. Children's Privacy**

Our website is not intended for children. We do not knowingly collect or maintain the personal information of children under the age of 13, and in some jurisdictions under the age of 16. If you are under the age of 13, please do not access our website at any time or in any manner. If we learn that we have collected personal information of children under the age of 13 or 16 (as applicable), we will take appropriate steps to delete that data. 

**8\. Sharing Data with Third Parties**

You might provide personal information directly to third parties as a consequence of your interactions with our website and other services offered by us. For example, our website may contain content and links to other third-party websites, plug-ins, and applications that are operated by third parties that may also operate cookies. Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. We don't control these third party websites or cookies, we are not responsible for their privacy statements, and this Privacy Policy does not apply to them. Please check the terms and conditions and privacy policy of the relevant third party website to find out how they collect and use your information. If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, contact us at using one of the methods described in the "Contact Us" section above. 

Please be responsible with personal information of others when using our website and the services available on it. We are not responsible for your misuse of personal information, or for the direct relationship between you and others that takes place outside of the website or our services. 

**9\. For California Residents: Your Privacy Rights and Do Not Track Disclosure**

AVTech Media Americas's policy is to share your personal information only if you have given us your consent, for instance, by your agreeing to this Privacy Policy through your use of our sites. After obtaining such consent, Safari may in accordance with this Privacy Policy from time to time provide its business partners with contact details for direct marketing purposes of relevant services, products, and programs. If you no longer wish your information to be shared, please let us know, and we will prevent disclosure of your information to such business partners free of charge, or if you have further inquiries regarding our information sharing practices, please let us know using the methods outlined in the "Contact Us" section above. 

California law requires us to let you know how we respond to web browser Do Not Track (DNT) signals. DNT is a way for users to inform websites and services that they do not want certain information about their webpage visits collected over time and across websites or online services. We do not respond to or honor DNT signals or similar mechanisms transmitted by web browsers at this time. 

**10\. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Please note that this Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your consent. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email or by means of a notice on this website prior to the change becoming effective.
